You did it. You built an amazing nodejs
application and in this course, we actually build a couple of applications and we're typically
not just doing this for our own practice or to do it on our PC only, instead we of course want to deploy
this application into the web so that it is reachable by other people
because as long as it's running on localhost, only you can reach it
and that is the idea during development of course.
Now in this module, we'll move from development to production and you will learn how we can prepare
our project for deployment.
There are some things we just want to adjust or where we want to make sure that we don't skip them.
We'll then of course also walk through all the important steps and the configuration you need to do to
deploy your project to a hosting provider
and we'll talk about security because that obviously is connected to deploying your app because as soon
as it does not run on your own computer anymore, you obviously have to make sure that some things just
are, well secure.
So let's dive into all these things in this module.